Hey guys,
welcome back to Obsession Car Detailing.
My name is Saad.
Okay, all of that, we just don't need. Hi,
guys. Welcome back. Welcome.
This is Saad. I'm sorry, but don't care.
So if we think of a car channel like
Carwow, "Hi, it's Matt Watson.
Today,
we're going to be here with four cars.
We're going to be doing a drag race
over..." It's, "What wins in a drag race
between an Audi RS Q8 Performance,
a Lamborghini Urus." Straight away,
the first
thing that comes out of his mouth
is the hook. What wins?
You go, "Fuck,
I'm not even really sure." "Well,
today," we're going into the
setup,
"we've got an Audi RS Q8 Performance,
we've got a Lamborghini Urus, we've
got a BMW M5 Competition, we've got this,
and we're going to find out which is
faster over the standing quarter mile."
Now, we've had the hook, we've had the
setup. "I'm Matt Watson,
welcome to Carwow." Boom.
So I then, in a Carwow video,
get to know exactly what it's about
and what I'm
going to get before he mentions who it is